Guide to the William David Allred Papers 1969-002
University of Houston Libraries Special Collections
- Political File, 1966-1980
  - Jones, Mr. & Mrs. George (Box 44)
  - Jones, Mr. H. T. (Box 44)
  - Jones, Harold (Box 44)
  - Jones, Hunter (Box 44)
  - Jones, Mr. J. Paul (Box 44)
  - Jones, Mrs. Jack W. (Box 44)
  - Jones, Mr. Johnie (Box 44)
  - Jones, Mr. & Mrs. Kenneth E. (Box 44)
  - Jones, Mr. & Mrs. Lee (Box 44)
  - Jones, Lorraine (Box 44)
  - Jones, Mr. & Mrs. Marion D. (Box 44)
  - Jones, Paul (Box 44)
  - Jones, Tommie L. (Box 44)
  - Jones, Mr. W. G. (Box 44)
  - Jones, Wanda J. (Box 44)
  - Jordan, Mr. & Mrs. Bryce (Box 44)
  - Jordan, Mr. Roy (Box 44)
  - Josey, Minnie (Box 44)
  - Joyce, Mr. Recil (Box 44)
  - Joymer, G. H. (Box 44)
  - Judicial Redistricting (Box 44)
  - Judicial Retirement (Box 44)
  - Juarez Race Track (Box 44)
  - Junge, Mr. J. A. (Box 44)
  - Jungmichel, Charlie (Box 44)
  - Junior Broiler Show (Box 44)
  - Junior Chamber of Commerce (Box 44)
  - Junior Colleges (Box 44)
  - Junior Service League of Wichita Falls (Box 44)
  - Junior Standard Club (Box 44)
  - Juvenile Delinquency (Box 44)
  - Jackson, Dr. Barry L. (Box 44)
  - Jackson, Mr. Clyde W. (Box 44)
  - Jackson, Fred H. (Box 44)
  - Jackson, Sen. Henry M. (Box 44)
  - Jackson, Lee F. (Box 44)
  - Jackson, Michael R. (Box 44)
  - Jackson, Mrs. W. V. (Box 44)
  - Jacobs, Mrs. Lila (Box 44)
  - Jahnke, Mr. & Mrs. Kenneth L. (Box 44)
  - Jails (Box 44)
  - James, Jesse (Box 44)
  - James, Mrs. Lena Ve (Box 44)
  - Janeke, Joe (Box 44)
  - Janota, Mrs. George F. (Box 44)
  - Jansen, Ms. Barbara Ann (Box 44)
  - January, Mr. & Mrs. Ken A. (Box 44)
  - Japan (Box 44)
  - Jarvis Christian College (Box 44)
  - Jaycees (Box 44)
  - Jeanis, Mr. Gayhart (Box 44)
  - Jeffers, Mrs. Florice Stripling (Box 44)
  - Jeffress, Mrs. Wallace (Box 44)
  - Jeffries, Mrs. Bonnie (Box 44)
  - Jenkins, John (Box 44)
  - Jenkins, Kenneth A. (Box 44)
  - Jenkins, Mrs. Sam A. (Box 44)
  - Jenkins, Terrie L. (Box 44)
  - Jenne, Mrs. W. T. (Box 44)
  - Jennings, Ms. Mary (Box 44)
  - Jessel, Ella May (Box 44)
  - Jeter, James (Box 44)
  - Jeter, John B. (Box 44)
  - Jett, Leiland (Box 44)
  - Jetton, Ms. Shelia (Box 44)
  - Jewelers (Box 44)
  - Shanke, Mrs. Ellen (Box 44)
  - Jimenez, Raymond (Box 44)
  - Jobe, Ms. Melinda (Box 44)
  - Job Seekers (Box 44)
  - Johnson, Alan (Box 44)
  - Johnson & Johnson (Box 44)
  - Johnson, Carl (Box 44)
  - Johnson, Ms. Cora L. (Box 44)
  - Johnson, Mr. & Mrs. David (Box 44)
  - Johnson, Dwight (Box 44)
  - Johnson, Eddie Bernice (Box 44)
  - Johnson, Rev. E. V. (Box 44)
  - Johnson, Frank (Box 44)
  - Johnson, Mrs. Helen A. (Box 44)
  - Johnson, Hurshel (Box 44)
  - Johnson Insulation Co., Inc. (Box 44)
  - Johnson, Mrs. J. A. (Box 44)
  - Johnson, Mr. & Mrs. James W. (Box 44)
  - Johnson, Jimmy (Box 44)
  - Johnson, Kenneth (Box 44)
  - Johnson, Mrs. Mabel (Box 44)
  - Johnson, Preston (Box 44)
  - Johnson, Mrs. Robbi (Box 44)
  - Johnson, Robert (Box 44)
  - Johnson, Ms. Ruth C. (Box 44)
  - Johnson, Ms. Vicki (Box 44)
  - Johnston, Ms. Bonnie (Box 44)
  - Johnston, James D. (Box 44)
  - John-Terrance Company (Box 44)
  - Jolliff, Mrs. Gus W. (Box 44)
  - Jones, Mrs. Bob (Box 44)
  - Jones, Mr. Clay (Box 44)
  - Jones, Curtis (Box 44)
  - Jones, Eldo M. M.D. (Box 44)
  - Jones, Mr. E. T. (Box 44)
  - Jones, Francis L. (Box 44)
  - Jones, Franklin Jr. (Box 44)
  - Jones, Gene (Box 44)
  - Jones, Mr. & Mrs. Glen D. (Box 44)
  - Jones, Hon. Grant (Box 44)
  - Jones, Ms. Gwen (Box 44)
  - Jones, Mr. Harold (Box 44)
  - Jones, Mr. & Mrs. James R. (Box 44)
  - Jones, Jeanette (Box 44)
  - Jones, Jerry (Box 44)
  - Jones, John D. (Box 44)
  - Jones, Mr. & Mrs. John P. (Box 44)
  - Jones, Leon (Box 44)
  - Jones, Lloyd A. (Box 44)
  - Jones, Luther (Box 44)
  - Jones, Ms. Mary Lou (Box 44)
  - Jones, Mrs. Oma (Box 44)
  - Jones, Robert C. (Box 44)
  - Jones, Mrs. T. L. (Box 44)
  - Jones, Ms. Valer Mae (Box 44)
  - Jones, William Mark (Box 44)
  - Joplin, Mrs. Wanda (Box 44)
  - Jordan, Adolphus (Box 44)
  - Jordan, Gene (Box 44)
  - Jordan, Mr. & Mrs. Omer (Box 44)
  - Jorgensen, Mr. Jerry D. (Box 44)
  - Joyner, Ms. Deborah L. (Box 44)
  - Judd, M. F. (Box 44)
  - Judge, Richard H. (Box 44)
  - Judicial Affairs Committee (Box 44)
  - Judicial Qualifications Committee (Box 44)
  - Junior Bar (Box 44)
  - Jury Service (Box 44)
  - Mr. Melvin Just (Box 44)
  - Justice, John (Box 44)
  - Justice (Box 44)
  - Health Security Action Council (Box 45)
  - Hearing Aids (Box 45)
  - Hearn, J. H. (Box 45)
  - Hearn, Joe T. (Box 45)
  - Hearn, Mrs. Pat (Box 45)
  - Hearn, Mrs. Virginia (Box 45)
  - Heath, Charles (Box 45)
  - Heatley, W.S. (Bill) (Box 45)
  - Hegwer, Andrew W. (Box 45)
  - Heikkinen, Mrs. Connie D. (Box 45)
  - Helmer, Clarence (Box 45)
  - Help Center (Box 45)
  - Helzlsouer, Mrs. Mary Margaret (Box 45)
  - Hemmi, Mrs. Alice (Box 45)
  - Hempling, Randall (Box 45)
  - Henderson, Don (Box 45)
  - Henderson, Hattie (Box 45)
  - Henderson, Howard (Box 45)
  - Henderson, Ms. Judith (Box 45)
  - Henderson, Mrs. R. W. (Box 45)
  - Henderson, Sandra (Box 45)
  - Hendricks, Rep. & Mrs. Bob (Box 45)
  - Hendricks, Mrs. Carol J. (Box 45)
  - Hendrickson, Kenneth (Box 45)
  - Hendrix, Ida Belle (Box 45)
  - Hendsbee, John B. (Box 45)
  - Hennelly, Mr. Tom F. (Box 45)
  - Henry, Mrs. Clydia Mae (Box 45)
  - Henry, Miss Mary Catherine (Box 45)
  - Henschel, Janine (Box 45)
  - Hensley, Ms. Jill (Box 45)
  - Hensley, Ms. Valerie (Box 45)
  - Herald, Sheila (Box 45)
  - Herd, Betty (Box 45)
  - Herd Safety (Box 45)
  - Herman, Timothy J. (Box 45)
  - Hermansen, Eric (Box 45)
  - Hernandez, Dr. Jose (Box 45)
  - Herod, Mrs. Grace (Box 45)
  - Herrera, Maria (Box 45)
  - Herring, Mr. Charles
  - Herrmann, Charles (Box 45)
  - Hertenstein, Dean I. (Box 45)
  - Herzfeld, Charles (Box 45)
  - Hester, Clarence (Box 45)
  - Hester, Tom (Box 45)
  - Heyser, Miss Shields (Box 45)
  - Hibbs, Hollie M. (Box 45)
  - Hibler, Mildred C. (Box 45)
  - Hickman, J. E. (Box 45)
  - Health Care Committee (Box 45)
  - Health Department (Box 45)
  - Heatlh Maintenance Organization (Box 45)
  - Haynes, Clyde Jr. (Box 45)
  - Haynes, Debbie (Box 45)
  - Haynesville (Box 45)
  - Haynie, Mattie Mae (Box 45)
  - Hays, Mrs. Eleanor (Box 45)
  - Hays, William H. (Box 45)
  - Heads, Manley (J.) (Box 45)
  - Hawn, Joe (Box 45)
  - Hawn, W. R. (Box 45)
  - Haws, B. T. (Box 45)
  - Hawthorne, Dr. Mary E. (Box 45)
  - Hay, Mr. & Mrs. John A. Jr. (Box 45)
  - Hay, Ruby Gist (Box 45)
  - Hayers, Mr. & Mrs. Paul H. (Box 45)
  - Hayes, Mr. & Mrs. Frank (Box 45)
  - Hayes, Karen (Box 45)
  - Hayley, Dr. C. C. (Box 45)
  - Hickman, Walter H. (Box 45)
  - Hicks, C. H. (Box 45)
  - Hicks, Clifford H. (Box 45)
  - Hicks, Clyde O. (Box 45)
  - Hicks, H. C. (Box 45)
  - Higgins, J. H. (Box 45)
  - Hightower, Miss Julie (Box 45)
  - Highways (Box 45)
  - Hilbers, Mr. Charles (Box 45)
  - Hill, Ms. Beulah (Box 45)
  - Hill, Miss Beverly (Box 45)
  - Hill, Dr. Charles (Box 45)
  - Hill, Dewey (Box 45)
  - Hill, Donald (Box 45)
  - Hill, Doris M. (Box 45)
  - Hill, Janie (Box 45)
  - Hill, Ms. Jeannie C. (Box 45)
  - Hill, Jim (Box 45)
  - Hill, Norma (Box 45)
  - Hill, Mr. Kenneth (Box 45)
  - Hill, T. B. (Box 45)
  - Hill, Mr. & Mrs. Victor L. (Box 45)
  - Hillard, Mr. William (Box 45)
  - Hillyer, James (Box 45)
  - Hinkle, J. C. (Box 45)
  - Hinote, Dorothy (Box 45)
  - Hinz, Herman (Box 45)
  - Hisel, Henry D. (Box 45)
  - Hitt, Howard M. (Box 45)
  - Hixon, Mrs. Nelda Jean (Box 45)
  - Hobbe, William E. (Box 45)
  - Hodge, H. P. (Box 45)
  - Hodges, Ms. Barbara (Box 45)
  - Hodges, Gerald (Box 45)
  - Hodges, Glenn M. (Box 45)
  - Hodges, Mattie (Box 45)
  - Hodges, Mr. & Mrs. R. E. (Box 45)
  - Hodges, Steve (Box 45)
  - Hodgkins, Mrs. Freda (Box 45)
  - Hoffman, Aileen H. (Box 45)
  - Hogan, Ms. Mary (Box 45)
  - Hogan, Mr. & Mrs. Roy (Box 45)
  - Hoggard, Earl R. (Box 45)
  - Hoggard, Mr. & Mrs. James (Box 45)
  - Hogue, Carl (Box 45)
  - Hogue, Miss Julia (Box 45)
  - Holbrook, Dr. & Mrs. Bill (Box 45)
  - Holbrook, Ray (Box 45)
  - Holcomb, Luther (Box 45)
  - Holcomb, Mr. & Mrs. Richard (Box 45)
  - Holdeman, Richard (Box 45)
  - Holden, Mrs. Frances M. (Box 45)
  - Holden, M. Wayne (Box 45)
  - Holdenak, Miss Helen (Box 45)
  - Holder in Due Course (Box 45)
  - Holder, Kenneth W. (Box 45)
  - Holland, Miss Alma De (Box 45)
  - Holland, Joe (Box 45)
  - Holland, Juanita (Box 45)
  - Holland, Louis T. (Box 45)
  - Holland, Steve (Box 45)
  - Hollandsworth, W. Ned (Box 45)
  - Holliday, Ian (Box 45)
  - Holliman, Dr. Niel B. (Box 45)
  - Holloman, Sergeant (Box 45)
  - Holloway, Mr. & Mrs. Lee A. (Box 45)
  - Hollowell, Bill (Box 45)
  - Holeman, Mrs. Billy (Box 45)
  - Holt, Robert G. (Box 45)
  - Homack, Don (Box 45)
  - Homan, Mrs. Philip L. (Box 45)
  - Home Economists (Box 45)
  - Home Health Agencies Associaiton of Texas (Box 45)
  - Homosexuality (Box 45)
  - Honesta, Sister M. (Box 45)
  - Hondo, Texas (Box 45)
  - Honorary Texans (Box 45)
  - Hood, James E. (Box 45)
  - Hooks, Rev. Robert (Box 45)
  - Hooser, A. H. "Jim" (Box 45)
  - Hopkins, Gladys (Box 45)
  - Hopkins, Harry (Box 45)
  - Horany, Jimmy P. (Box 45)
  - Horn, Helen C. (Box 45)
  - Horserace Gambling (Box 45)
  - Horton, Mrs. Alice A. (Box 45)
  - Horton, Bill (Box 45)
  - Horton, Miss Mona G. (Box 45)
  - Kadane, Edward G. (Box 46)
  - Kahan, Mrs. Frank (Box 46)
  - Karrenbrock, Mr. & Mrs. Homer (Box 46)
  - Kalski, Raymond (Box 46)
  - Kamay, Texas (Box 46)
  - Karl, Matthew (Box 46)
  - Karr, Mrs. O. H. (Box 46)
  - Karr, Mr. & Mrs. Truman James (Box 46)
  - Karrenbrock, Mr. Waldo E. (Box 46)
  - Kass, Alfred (Box 46)
  - Kass, Miriam (Box 46)
  - Kauer, Miss Marjorie (Box 46)
  - Kaufman, Abe (Box 46)
  - Kay, James S. (Box 46)
  - Kazen, Phillip A. (Box 46)
  - Kean, Mr. & Mrs. William (Box 46)
  - Keck, Miss Ruelene W. (Box 46)
  - Keene, Miss Sunny A. (Box 46)
  - Keith, Mr. & Mrs. W. E. (Box 46)
  - Kelly, Mrs. Donald (Box 46)
  - Kelly, Mrs. Jennie Lee (Box 46)
  - Kelly, Miss Louise (Box 46)
  - Kelly, Mrs. Mary (Box 46)
  - Kemp, Jack (Box 46)
  - Kemp Public Library (Box 46)
  - Kemper Insurance (Box 46)
  - Kennedy, Alton (Box 46)
  - Kennedy, Harold L. (Box 46)
  - Kennedy, Ms. Jeanetta (Box 46)
  - Kennedy, Vann M. (Box 46)
  - Kennelly, Miss Dottie (Box 46)
  - Kersey, E. E. Jr. (Box 46)
  - Key, Allan (Box 46)
  - Keyes, Earnest (Box 46)
  - Kidd, Mrs. Katherine (Box 46)
  - Kiel, Fred (Box 46)
  - Kiel, Jo (Box 46)
  - Kiel, Mrs. O. L. (Box 46)
  - Kiger, L. M. (Box 46)
  - Kilgore, Mr. Joe M. (Box 46)
  - Killebrew, Cupit, Rucker & Associates (Box 46)
  - Killebrew, Mr. James R. (Box 46)
  - Killeen, Texas (Box 46)
  - Killins, Mr. & Mrs. Bob (Box 46)
  - Killingsworth, Barton (Box 46)
  - Killingsworth, Maxine (Box 46)
  - Kilpatrick, Mrs. L. A. (Box 46)
  - Kilpatrick, Mr. Rufus (Box 46)
  - Kimbell, Mr. David (Box 46)
  - Kinch, Mr. Sam (Box 46)
  - Kinder, Mrs. Royal C. (Box 46)
  - Kindergartens (Box 46)
  - King Airlines (Box 46)
  - King, Beverly W. (Box 46)
  - King, Dyer (Box 46)
  - King, Miss Ethel (Box 46)
  - King, James A. (Box 46)
  - King, Mr. J. K. (Box 46)
  - King, Larry J. (Box 46)
  - King, Mrs. R. H. (Box 46)
  - Kinman, Mr. Charles D. (Box 46)
  - Kinsey, Miss Juanita (Box 46)
  - Kirby, Howard (Box 46)
  - Kirk, Mr. & Mrs. Clyde (Box 46)
  - Kirk, Mr. & Mrs. Stanley C. (Box 46)
  - Kirkham, Charles (Box 46)
  - Kirkham, Mrs. Frank (Box 46)
  - Kirklin, W. G. "Cotton" (Box 46)
  - Kirksey, Mr. Jay B. (Box 46)
  - Kirty, Leon (Box 46)
  - Kirkland, Ben (Box 46)
  - Kiselwick, Mrs. Dave (Box 46)
  - Kitchell, Mr. & Mrs. William G. (Box 46)
  - Kiwanis Clubs (Box 46)
  - Kinkerman, L. H. (Box 46)
  - Klous, Mrs. Austin F. (Box 46)
  - KLRN-TV (Box 46)
  - Knapp, Walter L. Jr. (Box 46)
  - Knezek, Mr. Leo (Box 46)
  - Knight, A. B. (Box 46)
  - Knight, C. D. (Box 46)
  - Knights of Columbus (Box 46)
  - Knight, Mr. James W. (Box 46)
  - Knight, Reuben (Box 46)
  - KNIN (Box 46)
  - Knowles, Joe C. (Box 46)
  - Knowles, Dr. John C. (Box 46)
  - Knox, Neal (Box 46)
  - Kolbe, Rev. & Mrs. Ed (Box 46)
  - Kolp, Mrs. Jimmie (Box 46)
  - Konkomp, Ms. Margaret (Box 46)
  - Koscot Interplanetary, inc. (Box 46)
  - Kosanke, John C. (Box 46)
  - Kouri, Mrs. A. Z. (Box 46)
  - Kouri, Philip S. (Box 46)
  - Kovack, P. M. (Box 46)
  - Krajca, John L. (Box 46)
  - Kressenberg, Mr. Dan (Box 46)
  - Kruger, Max (Box 46)
  - Lake Arrowhead (Box 46)
  - Lake Kickapoo (Box 46)
  - Lam, Elie (Box 46)
  - Lama, Mrs. Gus (Box 46)
  - Lamar Baptist Church (Box 46)
  - Lamb, Magann (Box 46)
  - Lambert, i. O. (Box 46)
  - Landscape Architects of Texas (Box 46)
  - Language Disabilities (Box 46)
  - Kuhn, E. M. (Box 46)
  - Kunkel, Melton (Box 46)
  - Kuykendall, Mr. & Mrs. H. G. (Box 46)
  - Lack, Emmett (Box 46)
  - Lambert, Larry (Box 46)
  - Lambright, Mr. Claude (Box 46)
  - Landers, Joseph (Box 46)
  - Lane, C. E. (Box 46)
  - Lane, Carlton J. (Box 46)
  - Lane, Edward (Box 46)
  - Lane, Mr. & Mrs. James F. (Jim) (Box 46)
  - Lane, Vetra A. (Box 46)
  - Lang, Mr. & Mrs. Charles B. (Box 46)
  - Lang, Mr. Sylvan (Box 46)
  - Langdon, Mr. & Mrs. Jim (Box 46)
  - Langford, Mr. & Mrs. David Kemp (Box 46)
  - Langford, E. W. (Box 46)
  - Langout, L. A. (Box 46)
  - Lanham, Fritz (Box 46)
  - Large, Howard (Box 46)
  - Largin, Mrs. Sonya L. (Box 46)
  - Larson, Mrs. G. Donald (Alisa) (Box 46)
  - Larson, Mr. & Mrs. John E. (Box 46)
  - Latta, Mr. & Mrs. Edwin F. G. (Box 46)
  - Lauck, Joe W. Jr. (Box 46)
  - Lauderdale, J. M. (Box 46)
  - Laughery, B. G. (Box 46)
  - Laukhuf, John R. Jr. (Box 46)
  - Laurence, Edith (Box 46)
  - Laughon, Tommy (Box 46)
  - Lavender, W. E. (Box 46)
  - Lavy, Mr. Jack (Box 46)
  - Lawfor, Mr. A. B. (Box 46)
  - Law Enforcement (Box 46)
  - Law Enforcement Pt. 2 (Box 46)
  - Law Enforcement Pt. 3 (Box 46)
  - Lawhorne, Mr. & Mrs. Cliff (Box 46)
  - Lawrence, Mrs. Edith (Box 46)
  - Lawrence, Gale (Box 46)
  - Lawrence, S. J. (Box 46)
  - Learner, Miss Karen (Box 46)
  - Leavell, Dr. Landrum (Box 46)
  - Lee, David (Box 46)
  - Lee, Dulen E. Jr. (Box 46)
  - Lee, J. P. (Box 46)
  - Lee, L. A. (Box 46)
  - Lee, Michael Stuart (Box 46)
  - Lee, Mickey L. (Box 46)
  - Lee, R. Ernest (Box 46)
  - Lee, Roger (Box 46)
  - Lefevre, Alice (Box 46)
  - League of Women Voters of Texas (Box 46)
  - Learning Disabilities (Box 46)
  - Legislative Internship (Box 46)
  - Legislative Reference Library (Box 46)
  - Legislative Wives Club (Box 46)
  - Legislature, 59th (Box 46)
  - Legislature, 60th (Box 46)
  - Legislature, 61st (Box 46)
  - Legilsature, 62nd (Box 46)
  - LeJeune, Mr. & Mrs. Winston (Box 46)
  - Leonard, Miss Angela (Box 46)
  - Leonard, Mr. & Mrs. Homer (Box 46)
  - Leah, Dan B. (Box 46)
  - Lester, Mrs. E. M. (Box 46)
  - Leveritt, O. B. (Box 46)
  - Levi Strauss & Co. (Box 46)
  - Levines (Box 46)
  - Leveridge, Mrs. A. T. Jr. (Box 46)
  - Lewis, Mr. & Mrs. Bob (Box 46)
  - Lewis, J. B. (Box 46)
  - Lewis, Mr. & Mrs. Jerry L. (Box 46)
  - Lewis, Miss Monterey (Box 46)
  - Lewis, S. L. (Box 46)
  - Labbe, Leonard C. (Box 47)
  - Labor (Box 47)
  - Laboratory Technicians (Box 47)
  - Lacey, A. M. (Box 47)
  - Ladd, Mrs. Lowell (Box 47)
  - Ladnier, Mary (Box 47)
  - LaHue, Mrs. Gearl (Box 47)
  - LaBelle, Mr. & Mrs. David (Box 47)
  - LVN's (Box 47)
  - Laboratory (Box 47)
  - LaCore, Robert E. (Box 47)
  - Lacy, Leonard L. (Box 47)
  - La Grange, Texas (Box 47)
  - Laird, Rev. Don (Box 47)
  - Laird, Lloyd (Box 47)
  - Lake Arrowhead State Park (Box 47)
  - Lake Travis (Box 47)
  - Lake Wichita (Box 47)
  - Lalor, Lance (Box 47)
  - Lamar University (Box 47)
  - Lamb, Ms. Kathy (Box 47)
  - Lambdin, Mrs. J. C. (Box 47)
  - Lambert, David D. (Box 47)
  - Lambert, Mrs. Pat H. (Box 47)
  - Lambert, Sid (Box 47)
  - Lamberth, A. W. (Box 47)
  - Lamm, Ms. Debbie (Box 47)
  - Lammers, J. B. (Box 47)
  - Lamme's Candies (Box 47)
  - Lanchart Industries, Inc. (Box 47)
  - Land (Box 47)
  - Land, Jim (Box 47)
  - Land, W. F. Jr. (Box 47)
  - Landis, Andrew J. (Box 47)
  - Landrum, Mike (Box 47)
  - Landscape Architects (Box 47)
  - Land Use (Box 47)
  - Landes, Mrs. Harold (Box 47)
  - Lane, Mrs. B. B. (Box 47)
  - Lane, Sharon (Box 47)
  - Lane, Charles C. (Box 47)
  - Lane, Ed (Box 47)
  - Lane, Fredrick Deshong (Box 47)
  - Lane, William E. (Box 47)
  - Laney, Pete (Box 47)
  - Laney, Sam (Box 47)
  - Lang, Jim (Box 47)
  - Lang, Ms. Pat (Box 47)
  - Langsdorf, Dena R. (Box 47)
  - La Porte, TX (Box 47)
  - Larance, Mrs. Betty (Box 47)
  - La Raza Unida (Box 47)
  - Laredo, Texas (Box 47)
  - Largin, W. D. (Box 47)
  - Larson, Arleen (Box 47)
  - Larson, Dr. & Mrs. Don (Box 47)
  - Larson, Mrs. Kenneth (Box 47)
  - Larue, Mr. & Mrs. Frank (Box 47)
  - Lary, Camm (Box 47)
  - Lashbaugh, Ms. Nancy (Box 47)
  - Latham, Doris Kay (Box 47)
  - Latimer, Mrs. Patricia A. (Box 47)
  - Latimer, Truett (Box 47)
  - Latta, Don (Box 47)
  - Latture, Paul (Box 47)
  - Lauch, Joe Jr. (Box 47)
  - Lauderdale, Virginia (Box 47)
  - Lauhoff, Herman (Box 47)
  - Laukhuf, Mrs. H. H. (Box 47)
  - Lavy, Ms. Cheryl (Box 47)
  - Lavy, L. L. (Box 47)
  - Law, Carl (Box 47)
  - Law, Mr. & Mrs. Charles R. (Box 47)
  - Law, Eloise (Box 47)
  - Lambrechtse Family (Box 47)
  - Leslie, Mrs. Pattie Zoe (Box 47)
  - Living Church (Box 47)
  - Lollis, Mr. & Mrs. David L. (Box 47)
  - Lopez, Mrs. Connie (Box 47)
  - Lutz, Mr. & Mrs. Roy (Box 47)
  - Liberals (Box 47)
  - License Plates (Box 47)
  - License Vocational Nurses (Box 47)
  - Licensed Vocational Nurses Association of Texas (Box 47)
  - Life Preservers (Box 47)
  - Lifetime Security Life Insurance Company (Box 47)
  - Ligard, Honore (Box 47)
  - Light, E. S. (Box 47)
  - Ligon, Dr. D. L. (Box 47)
  - Lile, Forest L. (Box 47)
  - Liles, Clifton (Box 47)
  - Lile & Prock Optical Service (Box 47)
  - Lillieo, Joan (Box 47)
  - Lamble, O. H. (Box 47)
  - Linam, R. H. (Box 47)
  - Lincoln Street Community Center (Box 47)
  - Lindsey, Ms. Mary Jo (Box 47)
  - Lington, Miss Eleanor M. (Box 47)
  - Link, Ms. Barbara (Box 47)
  - Lippard, Bob (Box 47)
  - Liquor (Box 47)
  - Liquor File 2 (Box 47)
  - Liquor File 3 (Box 47)
  - Liquor Control Board (Box 47)
  - Litonenko, Andrew J. (Box 47)
  - Litter (Box 47)
  - Little Cigar Council (Box 47)
  - Livestock (Box 47)
  - Loan Companies (Box 47)
  - Lobbyists (Box 47)
  - Local Law Publication (Box 47)
  - Lochridge, Mrs. Oscar E. (Box 47)
  - Lock, Ottis (Box 47)
  - Locke, Mr. Eugene (Box 47)
  - Locks, Sharon (Box 47)
  - Locker, David D. (Box 47)
  - Lockridge, Mr. & Mrs. Joe (Box 47)
  - Loden, Mrs. J. H. (Box 47)
  - Lodge, Don S. (Box 47)
  - Loftis, Mr. & Mrs. Edward W. (Box 47)
  - Loftis, Mr. Z. S. (Box 47)
  - Lofton, Archie (Box 47)
  - Logan, Robert Wayne (Box 47)
  - Loggie, Mrs. John (Box 47)
  - Lollar, Miss Nancy (Box 47)
  - Loyd, Mrs. A. L. (Box 47)
  - Loyd, Bud (Box 47)
  - Loyd, Mr. & Mrs. M. C. (Box 47)
  - LP-Gas (Box 47)
  - Lucas, Mr. & Mrs. W. D. (Box 47)
  - Lucy, Mrs. J. A. (Box 47)
  - Lubbock (Box 47)
  - Lucy, Patti Jeanette (Box 47)
  - Lucas, Mr. & Mrs. William D. (Box 47)
  - Ludy, Ben (Box 47)
  - Luckett, E. L. (Box 47)
  - Lumen, L. W. (Box 47)
  - Lumpkin, John Oscar II (Box 47)
  - Luna, Cecil (Box 47)
  - Luna, Mr. C. F. (Box 47)
  - Lunsford, Mrs. E. R. (Box 47)
  - Long, Mrs. Alton (Box 47)
  - Long, Miss Meredith (Box 47)
  - Long, Velma Mrs. (Box 47)
  - Longhorn Chevrolet Co. (Box 47)
  - Lord, Dorothy M. (Box 47)
  - Law Examiners (Box 48)
  - Lawler, Tammy (Box 48)
  - Laws, Cecil (Box 48)
  - Lawson, Joseph Odell (Box 48)
  - Lawson, Mr. & Mrs. W. D. Jr. (Box 48)
  - Lawyers (Box 48)
  - Lax, Ms. Nell (Box 48)
  - Lazenby, Mrs. O. A. (Box 48)
  - League of Conservation Voters (Box 48)
  - League of Latin American Citizens (Box 48)
  - League of Women Voters (Box 48)
  - League of Women Voters of Wichita Falls (Box 48)
  - Leath, Berneice (Box 48)
  - LeBeau, George L. Jr. (Box 48)
  - LeBeau, Mrs. George L. (Box 48)
  - Lebow, Mr. & Mrs. Larry (Box 48)
  - Ledbetter, Harry (Box 48)
  - Ledbetter, Leonard (Box 48)
  - Ledford, Mrs. H. P. (Box 48)
  - Lee, Mrs. Alice (Box 48)
  - Lee College (Box 48)
  - Lee, Mr. & Mrs. C. W. (Box 48)
  - Lee, Doyce R. (Box 48)
  - Lee, Rep. El Franco (Box 48)
  - Lee, Mrs. Frank (Box 48)
  - Lee, Mrs. Grace (Box 48)
  - Lee, Mr. & Mrs. N. A. Sr. (Box 48)
  - Lee, Ms. Pam (Box 48)
  - Lee, Mrs. Russell E. (Box 48)
  - Lee, Rev. Steve (Box 48)
  - Lee, Tracy (Box 48)
  - Leeper, Mr. James S. (Box 48)
  - Legal Procedure (Box 48)
  - Legalized Gambling (Box 48)
  - Leger, Margaret E. (Box 48)
  - Legis 50 (Box 48)
  - Legislative Budget Board (Box 48)
  - Legislative Chaplain (Box 48)
  - Legislative Council (Box 48)
  - Leland, George "Mickey" (Box 48)
  - Lemens, Vernon (Box 48)
  - Lemley, Jim (Box 48)
  - Lemmon, Ray (Box 48)
  - Lemmond, Morris (Box 48)
  - Lemond, B. (Box 48)
  - Lemond, Philip (Box 48)
  - Lemons, Walter J. (Box 48)
  - Lenhart, Bill (Box 48)
  - Leonard, Rep. Bob (Box 48)
  - Leopold, Jerilee (Box 48)
  - Lerew, Harold (Box 48)
  - Lesh, Dan B. (Box 48)
  - Leslie, Ms. Lois (Box 48)
  - Lester, Ms. Christine (Box 48)
  - Letendre, Mrs. Ann Jordan
  - Letteken, Mrs. Henry (Box 48)
  - Letter Carriers (Box 48)
  - Leuzinger, Dr. Donn E. (Box 48)
  - Leverett, Dr. C. L. (Box 48)
  - Levy, Mrs. Bernard (Box 48)
  - Lewallen, Mr. J. P. (Box 48)
  - Lewallen, Ms. Lois (Box 48)
  - Lewis, Chris (Box 48)
  - Lewis, Mrs. Edna (Box 48)
  - Lewis,Mrs. Faye (Box 48)
  - Lewis, Gibson D. (Box 48)
  - Lewis, Mr. & Mrs. Gordon (Box 48)
  - Lewis, Jerry (Box 48)
  - Lewis, Ms. K. Lynn (Box 48)
  - Lewis, Mrs. Marie (Box 48)
  - Lewis, Michael D. (Box 48)
  - Lewis, Richardia (Box 48)
  - Lewis, Ronnie (Box 48)
  - Lewis, Stephanie (Box 48)
  - Lewis, Mr. & Mrs. W. M. (Box 48)
  - Lewis, Mr. & Mrs. W. R. (Box 48)
  - Leyden, Mr. Edward E. (Box 48)
  - Liberty County (Box 48)
  - Liberty Hill, Texas (Box 48)
  - Librarians (Box 48)
  - Libraries (Box 48)
  - Libraries File 2 (Box 48)
  - Lichie, Mrs. Gene (Box 48)
  - Life Flight (Box 48)
  - Likin, Rev. W. A. (Box 48)
  - Lincoln, Ms. Kay Ann (Box 48)
  - Lindsay, Ms. Mina (Box 48)
  - Lindsey, Mrs. Kenneth (Box 48)
  - Lingle, Mr. & Mrs. Wesley (Box 48)
  - Linn, Travis (Box 48)
  - Lions Club (Box 48)
  - Lippard, C. J. (Box 48)
  - Lips, Leslie E. (Box 48)
  - Liquor Nov. 1979 File 3 (Box 48)
  - Liquor 77 (Box 48)
  - Liquor 1974-1976 (Box 48)
  - Liquor Regulation (Box 48)
  - Liquor Regulation Committee 1975 (Box 48)
  - Litteken, Mr. & Mrs. Arthur H. (Box 48)
  - Litteken, Etta Mae (Pug) (Box 48)
  - Litteken, Mr. & Mrs. Henry (Box 48)
  - Litteken, Mr. & Mrs. Ted H. (Box 48)
  - Little, Leon (Box 48)
  - Little, Ora (Box 48)
  - Living Bank (Box 48)
  - Loans (Box 48)
  - Loan Firms (Box 48)
  - Loan Sharks (Box 48)
  - Lobley, Mr. & Mrs. Harold (Box 48)
  - Local Government (Box 48)
  - Locke, R. K. (Box 48)
  - Locke, Tom (Box 48)
  - Lockhart, Carrol (Box 48)
  - Lockhart, Edna (Box 48)
  - Lockhart, Jeffery Scott (Box 48)
  - Lockwood Corporation (Box 48)
  - Logan, Ms. Florence Elaine (Box 48)
  - Logg, William E. (Box 48)
  - Loh, Mr. Harold Van (Box 48)
  - Lohmann, Mrs. H. H. (Box 48)
  - Lofland, TommyeLoggie, Mrs. W. R. (Box 48)
  - Lohrmann, Charles (Box 48)
  - Lombardino, Frank (Box 48)
  - London, F. M. (Box 48)
  - London, Jack (Box 48)
  - London, Mrs. Letitia (Box 48)
  - London, Hon. Marvin F. (Box 48)
  - London, Mr. Ronnie (Box 48)
  - Lone Star Alliance (Box 48)
  - Lone Star Gas Company (Box 48)
  - Long, Dave (Box 48)
  - Long, Ms. Kathleen R. (Box 48)
  - Long, Ruby (Box 48)
  - Long, Stuart (Box 48)
  - Longest, Tom B. (Box 48)
  - Longoria, St. Sen. Raul (Box 48)
  - Longview, Texas (Box 48)
  - Looney, Rep. Cullen R. (Box 48)
  - Looney, Ms. Delores (Box 48)
  - Lopez, Ms. Angelina (Box 48)
  - Lotteries (Box 48)